export default [
  {
    id: "q1",
    question: "Pertanyaan 1",
    answers: ["benar", "salah1", "salah2", "salah3"],
  },
  {
    id: "q2",
    question: "Pertanyaan 2",
    answers: ["benar", "wrong", "false", "salah4"],
  },
  {
    id: "q3",
    question: "Pertanyaan 3",
    answers: ["benar", "salahw", "salaha", "salahb"],
  },
  {
    id: "q4",
    question: "Pertanyaan 4",
    answers: ["benar", "salahf", "salahd", "salahr"],
  },
  {
    id: "q5",
    question: "Pertanyaan 5",
    answers: ["benar", "falsy", "undifined", "null"],
  },
  {
    id: "q6",
    question: "Pertanyaan 6",
    answers: ["benar", "!benar", "salah banget", "salah woy"],
  },
  {
    id: "q7",
    question: "Pertanyaan 7",
    answers: ["benar", "salah ini", "jangan pilih ini", "salah salah salah"],
  },
  {
    id: "q8",
    question: "Pertanyaan 8",
    answers: ["benar", "salah wwwww", "salah 2111212", "salah 123"],
  },
  {
    id: "q9",
    question: "Pertanyaan 9",
    answers: ["benar", "salah", "salah", "salah"],
  },
  {
    id: "q10",
    question: "Pertanyaan 10",
    answers: ["benar", "salah", "salah", "salah"],
  },
];
